<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cuisine</string>


    <string name="day_1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day1">Ugali and Sukuma Wiki</string>
    <string name="day_1_description">A staple Kenyan dish made with maize flour and served with braised collard greens.</string>


    <string name="day_2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day2">Nyama Choma</string>
    <string name="day_2_description">Nyama Choma, which translates to "roasted meat" in Swahili, is a beloved dish in Kenya and across
        East Africa. It is a simple yet flavorful dish that highlights the natural taste of the meat,
        which is typically marinated with a mixture of spices and grilled over an open flame until tender and charred.</string>


    <string name="day_3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day3">Chapati</string>
    <string name="day_3_description">Chapati is a staple food in Kenyan cuisine, often served alongside
        main dishes such as stews, curries, or grilled meats. It is a type of unleavened flatbread made from
        a simple dough of flour, water, salt, and sometimes oil or fat. Chapati is known for its soft and flaky texture,
        making it a delicious accompaniment to a wide variety of dishes.</string>


    <string name="day_4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day4">Githeri</string>
    <string name="day_4_description">Githeri, a traditional Kenyan dish made from a hearty mixture of maize (corn) and beans,
        typically cooked together until tender and seasoned with various spices.</string>


    <string name="day_5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day5"> Mandazi</string>
    <string name="day_5_description">Mandazi is a beloved snack in Kenya and other East African countries,
        often enjoyed with tea or coffee for breakfast or as a sweet treat throughout the day.
        These deep-fried doughnuts are soft on the inside and slightly crispy on the outside, with a hint of sweetness and aromatic spices.</string>


    <string name="day_6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day6">Samosa</string>
    <string name="day_6_description">Samosas are savory, triangular-shaped pastries filled with a mixture of spiced potatoes, peas,
        and sometimes meat, then deep-fried until golden brown and crispy.
        They are a beloved snack in Kenya and are often enjoyed as appetizers or street food.</string>


    <string name="day_7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day7">Pilau</string>
    <string name="day_7_description">Pilau is a classic dish in Kenyan cuisine, known for its rich spices, tender meat, and aromatic rice.
        It is often served during festive occasions, celebrations, and family gatherings.</string>


    <string name="day_8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day8">Matoke</string>
    <string name="day_8_description">Matoke is a traditional dish that originated from
        Uganda but is also widely enjoyed in Kenya and other East African countries. It is made from green bananas,
        also known as cooking bananas or plantains, which are peeled, chopped, and cooked until tender.
        Matoke can be prepared in various ways, but one common method involves stewing the bananas with onions,
        tomatoes, and spices to create a flavorful and hearty dish.</string>


    <string name="day_9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day9">Mursik</string>
    <string name="day_9_description">Mursik is a unique and culturally significant beverage in Kenya, known for its distinctive fermented flavor.
        It is traditionally made by fermenting cows milk in a specially prepared gourd known as a "sotet" or "sotit."
        The gourd is charred on the inside to impart a smoky flavor to the milk, and ash from certain plants is added to aid in the fermentation process.
        Mursik is typically consumed as a refreshing drink, and it is also believed to have various health benefits..</string>


    <string name="day_10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day10">Kenyan Masala Chips</string>
    <string name="day_10_description">Kenyan Masala Chips are a delicious and indulgent snack or
        side dish commonly found in street food stalls and local eateries throughout Kenya. These crispy French fries are
        elevated with the addition of a special masala spice blend,
        which gives them a unique and aromatic flavor</string>


    <string name="day_11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day11">Mahamri</string>
    <string name="day_11_description">Mahamri is a traditional Kenyan pastry that is similar
        to doughnuts but with a slightly different texture and flavor profile.
        It is often enjoyed as a breakfast dish or as a sweet treat with tea or coffee.</string>


    <string name="day_12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day12"> Kenyan Beef Stew</string>
    <string name="day_12_description">Slow-cooked beef stew with potatoes, carrots, and other vegetables, seasoned with Kenyan spices.</string>


    <string name="day_13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day13">Kachumbari</string>
    <string name="day_13_description">Kachumbari is a popular Kenyan salad known for its simplicity and refreshing flavors.
        It is often served as a side dish or accompaniment to grilled meats, stews, or rice dishes.
        This salad is particularly popular during gatherings, celebrations, and outdoor barbecues.</string>


    <string name="day_14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day14">Fish in Coconut Sauce</string>
    <string name="day_14_description">Fish in Coconut Sauce is a beloved dish along the Kenyan coast,
        where seafood is abundant and coconut is a common ingredient in many dishes.
        This dish typically features fresh fish cooked in a creamy coconut curry sauce infused with aromatic spices.</string>


    <string name="day_15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day15">Ugali and Omena </string>
    <string name="day_15_description">Ugali is a fundamental part of the Kenyan diet and is made from maize flour (also known as cornmeal) cooked with water to a thick, dough-like consistency.
        It serves as a staple carbohydrate and is commonly eaten alongside various meat, vegetable, or fish dishes.
Omena, also known as "dagaa" in some regions, are tiny dried fish that are a popular ingredient in Kenyan cooking,
        especially in the Lake Victoria region. They are rich in protein, omega-3 fatty acids, and other nutrients,
        making them a nutritious addition to meals.</string>


    <string name="day_16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day16">Kenyan Tea</string>
    <string name="day_16_description">Strong black tea with milk and sugar, often enjoyed with mandazi or chapati.</string>


    <string name="day_17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day17">Mukimo</string>
    <string name="day_17_description">Mukimo is a beloved dish in Kenyan cuisine, particularly among the Kikuyu ethnic group,
        although it is enjoyed by people from various backgrounds across the country.
        It is a hearty and flavorful dish that combines mashed potatoes with other ingredients to create a delicious and satisfying meal.</string>


    <string name="day_18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day18">Kenyan Vegetable Curry</string>
    <string name="day_18_description">A flavorful curry made with mixed vegetables and coconut milk.</string>


    <string name="day_19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day19">Mbaazi</string>
    <string name="day_19_description">Mbaazi is a popular dish in Kenya, especially along the coastal regions, where it is often enjoyed as a breakfast dish or as a side dish for lunch or dinner.
        It is made from pigeon peas, also known as Congo peas or gungo peas, which are simmered in creamy coconut milk along with aromatic spices.</string>


    <string name="day_20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day20">Kenyan Chicken Curry</string>
    <string name="day_20_description">Kenyan Chicken Curry is a popular dish enjoyed across the country, known for its bold flavors and comforting appeal. It combines tender chicken pieces
        with a fragrant curry sauce made from a blend of spices and other ingredients.</string>


    <string name="day_21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day21">Chili Scrambled Eggs</string>
    <string name="day_21_description">Chili Scrambled Eggs is a simple yet flavorful dish made by whisking together eggs with
        chopped chili peppers and seasoning, then cooking them until fluffy and fully set</string>


    <string name="day_22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day22"> Beef Pilau</string>
    <string name="day_22_description">Fragrant rice dish cooked with beef, spices, and caramelized onions.</string>


    <string name="day_23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day23">Bhajia</string>
    <string name="day_23_description">Spicy potato fritters, often served as a snack or appetizer.</string>


    <string name="day_24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day24">Irio</string>
    <string name="day_24_description">Mashed potatoes mixed with peas, corn, and sometimes spinach, a traditional Kikuyu dish.</string>


    <string name="day_25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day25">Kenyan Beef Biriyani</string>
    <string name="day_25_description">Fragrant rice dish cooked with beef, vegetables, and aromatic spices.</string>


    <string name="day_26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day26">Kenyan Lentil Soup</string>
    <string name="day_26_description"> Hearty soup made with lentils, tomatoes, and Kenyan spices.</string>


    <string name="day_27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day27">Kenyan Fried Fish</string>
    <string name="day_27_description">Crispy fried fish seasoned with Kenyan spices, often served with ugali.</string>


    <string name="day_28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day28">Fried Beans</string>
    <string name="day_28_description"> A common dish made from cooked beans sautéed with onions, tomatoes, and spices.</string>


    <string name="day_29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="day29">Fried Sosi</string>
    <string name="day_29_description">"Well-fried sosi soya chunks" refers to a dish made with soya chunks, also known as textured vegetable protein (TVP) or soy meat, seasoned and fried until crispy and well-cooked.</string>


    <string name="day_30">Day 30</string>
    <string name="day30">Ndengu</string>
    <string name="day_30_description"> Green grams (mung beans) cooked with onions, tomatoes, and spices, a nutritious and popular dish in Kenya.</string>

</resources>